[
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 0,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Me only",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 8,
          "prompt": "Are you applying by yourself or with another applicant?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
          "order": 200
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 1,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Husband, Wife, Father",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Relationship_With_SecondApplicant",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 9,
          "prompt": "What is your relationship with the 2nd applicant?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Relationship_With_SecondApplicant",
          "order": 720
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 0,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Me only",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 8,
              "prompt": "Are you applying by yourself or with another applicant?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
              "order": 200
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846976,
            "start": 0,
            "end": 1,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Number_of_Applicants=Yes",
              "order": 720
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846976",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 1,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Husband, Wife, Father",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Relationship_With_SecondApplicant",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 9,
              "prompt": "What is your relationship with the 2nd applicant?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Relationship_With_SecondApplicant",
              "order": 720
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 2,
        "labels": [
          "Section"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "name": "Living Situation ",
          "sectionId": "Living Situation "
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:2"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 3,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_AddressCheck",
          "stage": "",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "",
          "sectionOrder": 0,
          "prompt": "Is this Your current Address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_AddressCheck",
          "order": 721
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 2,
            "labels": [
              "Section"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "name": "Living Situation ",
              "sectionId": "Living Situation "
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:2"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846978,
            "start": 2,
            "end": 3,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "EXISTS { MATCH (a:Applicant {applicantId: $applicantId})-[:ANSWERED]->(:Datapoint)-[:ANSWERS]->(:Question {questionId: \"Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)\"}) }",
              "order": 721
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846978",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:2",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 3,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_AddressCheck",
              "stage": "",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "",
              "sectionOrder": 0,
              "prompt": "Is this Your current Address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_AddressCheck",
              "order": 721
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 3,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_AddressCheck",
          "stage": "",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "",
          "sectionOrder": 0,
          "prompt": "Is this Your current Address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_AddressCheck",
          "order": 721
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 4,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Owned Outright",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
          "stage": "M10",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] [current/prior] residential status?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
          "order": 730
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 3,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_AddressCheck",
              "stage": "",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "",
              "sectionOrder": 0,
              "prompt": "Is this Your current Address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_AddressCheck",
              "order": 721
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846979,
            "start": 3,
            "end": 4,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "EXISTS { MATCH (a:Applicant {applicantId: $applicantId})-[:ANSWERED]->(:Datapoint)-[:ANSWERS]->(:Question {questionId: \"Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)\"}) }",
              "order": 730
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846979",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:3",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 4,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Owned Outright",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
              "stage": "M10",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] [current/prior] residential status?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
              "order": 730
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 4,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Owned Outright",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
          "stage": "M10",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] [current/prior] residential status?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
          "order": 730
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 5,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current residential address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Current)",
          "order": 740
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 4,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Owned Outright",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
              "stage": "M10",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] [current/prior] residential status?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer)",
              "order": 730
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846980,
            "start": 4,
            "end": 5,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "EXISTS { MATCH (a:Applicant {applicantId: $applicantId})-[:ANSWERED]->(:Datapoint {fieldId:\"F_AD_AddressCheck\", typedValue:\"No\"}) }",
              "order": 740
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846980",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:4",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 5,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current residential address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Current)",
              "order": 740
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 5,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current residential address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Current)",
          "order": 740
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 6,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Overseas_Address",
          "stage": "App",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "Does applicant live overseas?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Overseas_Address",
          "order": 750
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 5,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerCurrent)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current residential address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Current)",
              "order": 740
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846981,
            "start": 5,
            "end": 6,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer) = Oveseas",
              "order": 750
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846981",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:5",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 6,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Overseas_Address",
              "stage": "App",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "Does applicant live overseas?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Overseas_Address",
              "order": 750
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 6,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Overseas_Address",
          "stage": "App",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "Does applicant live overseas?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Overseas_Address",
          "order": 750
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 7,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "5 years, 2 months",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Date",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [lived/live] here (in years and months)?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
          "order": 760
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 6,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Overseas_Address",
              "stage": "App",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "Does applicant live overseas?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Overseas_Address",
              "order": 750
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846982,
            "start": 6,
            "end": 7,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "-",
              "order": 760
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846982",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:6",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 7,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "5 years, 2 months",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Date",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [lived/live] here (in years and months)?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
              "order": 760
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 7,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "5 years, 2 months",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Date",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [lived/live] here (in years and months)?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
          "order": 760
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 8,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerPrior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior residential address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Prior)",
          "order": 770
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 7,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "5 years, 2 months",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Date",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [lived/live] here (in years and months)?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer)",
              "order": 760
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846983,
            "start": 7,
            "end": 8,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Residential_Start_Date_(Customer) < 24 months",
              "order": 770
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846983",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:7",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 8,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerPrior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior residential address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Prior)",
              "order": 770
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 8,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerPrior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior residential address?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Prior)",
          "order": 770
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 9,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "1",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "How many individuals are on the lease?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
          "order": 780
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 8,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "164 Booran Road, Glen Huntly, VIC 3163",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Residential_Address_(CustomerPrior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior residential address?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Residential_Address_(Customer-Prior)",
              "order": 770
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846984,
            "start": 8,
            "end": 9,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer) = Renting",
              "order": 780
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846984",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:8",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 9,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "1",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "How many individuals are on the lease?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
              "order": 780
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 9,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "1",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "How many individuals are on the lease?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
          "order": 780
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 10,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "$1,500,000",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Property_Value",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Integer",
          "sectionOrder": 7,
          "prompt": "When is the estimated value of this property?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Property_Value",
          "order": 790
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:10"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 9,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "1",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "How many individuals are on the lease?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Individuals_on_Lease",
              "order": 780
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846985,
            "start": 9,
            "end": 10,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Residential_Status_(Customer) = Outright Owner",
              "order": 790
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846985",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:9",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:10"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 10,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "$1,500,000",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Property_Value",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Integer",
              "sectionOrder": 7,
              "prompt": "When is the estimated value of this property?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Property_Value",
              "order": 790
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:10"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 11,
        "labels": [
          "Section"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "name": "Employment ",
          "sectionId": "Employment "
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:11"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 12,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Employed",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Status",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Multi)",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment status?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Status",
          "order": 800
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 11,
            "labels": [
              "Section"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "name": "Employment ",
              "sectionId": "Employment "
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:11"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846987,
            "start": 11,
            "end": 12,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "-",
              "order": 800
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846987",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:11",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 12,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Employed",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Status",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Multi)",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment status?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Status",
              "order": 800
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 12,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Employed",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Status",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Multi)",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment status?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Status",
          "order": 800
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 13,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment type?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
          "order": 810
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 12,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Employed",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Status",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Multi)",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment status?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Status",
              "order": 800
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846988,
            "start": 12,
            "end": 13,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Status = Employed",
              "order": 810
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846988",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:12",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 13,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment type?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
              "order": 810
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 13,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment type?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
          "order": 810
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 14,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current occupation?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
          "order": 820
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 13,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current employment type?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Current)",
              "order": 810
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846989,
            "start": 13,
            "end": 14,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Status = Employed",
              "order": 820
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846989",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:13",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 14,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current occupation?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
              "order": 820
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 14,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current occupation?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
          "order": 820
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 15,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "22-Dec-19",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Date",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [worked/work] here (in years and months)?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
          "order": 830
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 14,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] current occupation?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Current)",
              "order": 820
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846990,
            "start": 14,
            "end": 15,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Status = Employed",
              "order": 830
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846990",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:14",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 15,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "22-Dec-19",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Date",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [worked/work] here (in years and months)?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
              "order": 830
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 15,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "22-Dec-19",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Date",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [worked/work] here (in years and months)?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
          "order": 830
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 16,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Full Time",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior employment type?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
          "order": 840
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 15,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "22-Dec-19",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Date",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "How long [have/did] [you/they] [worked/work] here (in years and months)?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Time_Period",
              "order": 830
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846991,
            "start": 15,
            "end": 16,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period < 24 months",
              "order": 840
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846991",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:15",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 16,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Full Time",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior employment type?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
              "order": 840
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 16,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Full Time",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior employment type?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
          "order": 840
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 17,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Plumber",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior occupation?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
          "order": 850
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 16,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Full Time",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior employment type?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Type(Prior)",
              "order": 840
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846992,
            "start": 16,
            "end": 17,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period < 24 months",
              "order": 850
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846992",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:16",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 17,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Plumber",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior occupation?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
              "order": 850
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 17,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Plumber",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior occupation?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
          "order": 850
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 18,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Coles",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employer_Name",
          "stage": "App",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 7,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] employer's company name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employer_Name",
          "order": 860
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 17,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Plumber",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] prior occupation?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employment_Occupation(Prior)",
              "order": 850
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846993,
            "start": 17,
            "end": 18,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Status = Employed",
              "order": 860
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846993",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:17",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 18,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Coles",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employer_Name",
              "stage": "App",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 7,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] employer's company name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employer_Name",
              "order": 860
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 18,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Coles",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Employer_Name",
          "stage": "App",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 7,
          "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] employer's company name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Employer_Name",
          "order": 860
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 19,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Probation",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Application",
          "dataType": "Boolean",
          "sectionOrder": 8,
          "prompt": "Are [you/they] on probation?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Probation",
          "order": 870
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:19"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 18,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Coles",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Employer_Name",
              "stage": "App",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 7,
              "prompt": "What [is/was] [your/their] employer's company name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Employer_Name",
              "order": 860
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606846994,
            "start": 18,
            "end": 19,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "Q_AD_Employment_Time_Period < 1 year",
              "order": 870
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606846994",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:18",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:19"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 19,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Probation",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Application",
              "dataType": "Boolean",
              "sectionOrder": 8,
              "prompt": "Are [you/they] on probation?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Probation",
              "order": 870
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:19"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 28,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Perkins",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Last_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "What is your last name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Last_Name",
          "order": 50
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 29,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Male",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Gender",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "What is your gender?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Gender",
          "order": 60
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 28,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Perkins",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Last_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "What is your last name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Last_Name",
              "order": 50
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847004,
            "start": 28,
            "end": 29,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 60
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847004",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 29,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Male",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Gender",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "What is your gender?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Gender",
              "order": 60
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 29,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Male",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Gender",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 4,
          "prompt": "What is your gender?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Gender",
          "order": 60
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 30,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Refinance",
          "questionId": "Q_LD_Loan_Purpose",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What is the purpose of the loan?",
          "fieldId": "F_LD_Loan_Purpose",
          "order": 110
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 29,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Male",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Gender",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 4,
              "prompt": "What is your gender?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Gender",
              "order": 60
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847005,
            "start": 29,
            "end": 30,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 110
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847005",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:29",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 30,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Refinance",
              "questionId": "Q_LD_Loan_Purpose",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What is the purpose of the loan?",
              "fieldId": "F_LD_Loan_Purpose",
              "order": 110
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 30,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Refinance",
          "questionId": "Q_LD_Loan_Purpose",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 5,
          "prompt": "What is the purpose of the loan?",
          "fieldId": "F_LD_Loan_Purpose",
          "order": 110
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 31,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Car",
          "questionId": "Q_VD_Asset_Type",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "What type of vehicle do you want to buy?",
          "fieldId": "F_LD_Asset_Type",
          "order": 120
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 30,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Refinance",
              "questionId": "Q_LD_Loan_Purpose",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 5,
              "prompt": "What is the purpose of the loan?",
              "fieldId": "F_LD_Loan_Purpose",
              "order": 110
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847006,
            "start": 30,
            "end": 31,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 120
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847006",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:30",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 31,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Car",
              "questionId": "Q_VD_Asset_Type",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "What type of vehicle do you want to buy?",
              "fieldId": "F_LD_Asset_Type",
              "order": 120
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 31,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Car",
          "questionId": "Q_VD_Asset_Type",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 6,
          "prompt": "What type of vehicle do you want to buy?",
          "fieldId": "F_LD_Asset_Type",
          "order": 120
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 32,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
          "questionId": "Q_VD_EV_Status",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Boolean",
          "sectionOrder": 7,
          "prompt": "Is the vehicle an electric vehicle (EV)?",
          "fieldId": "F_VD_EV_Status",
          "order": 130
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 31,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Car",
              "questionId": "Q_VD_Asset_Type",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 6,
              "prompt": "What type of vehicle do you want to buy?",
              "fieldId": "F_LD_Asset_Type",
              "order": 120
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847007,
            "start": 31,
            "end": 32,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 130
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847007",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:31",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 32,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
              "questionId": "Q_VD_EV_Status",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Boolean",
              "sectionOrder": 7,
              "prompt": "Is the vehicle an electric vehicle (EV)?",
              "fieldId": "F_VD_EV_Status",
              "order": 130
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 32,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
          "questionId": "Q_VD_EV_Status",
          "stage": "Qualify",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Boolean",
          "sectionOrder": 7,
          "prompt": "Is the vehicle an electric vehicle (EV)?",
          "fieldId": "F_VD_EV_Status",
          "order": 130
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 0,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Me only",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
          "stage": "Magic 10",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
          "sectionOrder": 8,
          "prompt": "Are you applying by yourself or with another applicant?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
          "order": 200
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 32,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Yes",
              "questionId": "Q_VD_EV_Status",
              "stage": "Qualify",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Boolean",
              "sectionOrder": 7,
              "prompt": "Is the vehicle an electric vehicle (EV)?",
              "fieldId": "F_VD_EV_Status",
              "order": 130
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847008,
            "start": 32,
            "end": 0,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 200
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847008",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:32",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 0,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Me only",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
              "stage": "Magic 10",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "Enum (Single)",
              "sectionOrder": 8,
              "prompt": "Are you applying by yourself or with another applicant?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Number_of_Applicants",
              "order": 200
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:0"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 36,
        "labels": [
          "Section"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "name": "Get a Quote",
          "sectionId": "Get a Quote"
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:36"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 37,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Jessica",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_First_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What is your first name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_First_Name",
          "order": 30
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 36,
            "labels": [
              "Section"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "name": "Get a Quote",
              "sectionId": "Get a Quote"
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:36"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847012,
            "start": 36,
            "end": 37,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 30
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847012",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:36",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 37,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Jessica",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_First_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What is your first name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_First_Name",
              "order": 30
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 37,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Jessica",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_First_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 1,
          "prompt": "What is your first name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_First_Name",
          "order": 30
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 38,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Rachel",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Middle_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What is your middle name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Middle_Name",
          "order": 40
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 37,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Jessica",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_First_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 1,
              "prompt": "What is your first name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_First_Name",
              "order": 30
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847013,
            "start": 37,
            "end": 38,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 40
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847013",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:37",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 38,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Rachel",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Middle_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What is your middle name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Middle_Name",
              "order": 40
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  },
  {
    "p": {
      "start": {
        "identity": 38,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Rachel",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Middle_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 2,
          "prompt": "What is your middle name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Middle_Name",
          "order": 40
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38"
      },
      "end": {
        "identity": 28,
        "labels": [
          "Question"
        ],
        "properties": {
          "exampleAnswer": "Perkins",
          "questionId": "Q_AD_Last_Name",
          "stage": "CR",
          "heading": "Get Quote",
          "dataType": "String",
          "sectionOrder": 3,
          "prompt": "What is your last name?",
          "fieldId": "F_AD_Last_Name",
          "order": 50
        },
        "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28"
      },
      "segments": [
        {
          "start": {
            "identity": 38,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Rachel",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Middle_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 2,
              "prompt": "What is your middle name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Middle_Name",
              "order": 40
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38"
          },
          "relationship": {
            "identity": 1152921504606847014,
            "start": 38,
            "end": 28,
            "type": "PRECEDES",
            "properties": {
              "askWhen": "",
              "order": 50
            },
            "elementId": "5:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:1152921504606847014",
            "startNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:38",
            "endNodeElementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28"
          },
          "end": {
            "identity": 28,
            "labels": [
              "Question"
            ],
            "properties": {
              "exampleAnswer": "Perkins",
              "questionId": "Q_AD_Last_Name",
              "stage": "CR",
              "heading": "Get Quote",
              "dataType": "String",
              "sectionOrder": 3,
              "prompt": "What is your last name?",
              "fieldId": "F_AD_Last_Name",
              "order": 50
            },
            "elementId": "4:b7bb25e2-6c90-4915-ac6b-1acc220d982b:28"
          }
        }
      ],
      "length": 1.0
    }
  }
]